dreamscloud.com 2017-06-11

# Online Dream Interpretation, Meaning & Analysis | DreamsCloud

This is the Privacy Policy for DreamsCloud and the DreamsCloud’s www.dreamscloud.com website ("Site"), which is operated by Dreams Book, Inc ("DBI"). Your privacy is important to us, and we provide this Privacy Policy regarding our online collection, use and disclosure practices to help you to make informed decisions regarding use of this site, and exercising choices regarding our collection, use and disclosure of the personal information about you from this website. Please visit the "Sharing & Privacy" section of your Profile Page to adjust your privacy settings.

The definitions for terms that are capitalized in this document but not defined herein can be found in the DreamsCloud’s Terms of Use. The Terms of Use are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy. To view the Terms of Use, click here

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE DREAMS CLOUD’S TERMS OF USE.

We take your privacy very seriously. In designing our site, we have taken extra care to protect your privacy. All content within your profile has a privacy option. However, regardless of our efforts, it is your responsibility to control your sharing and privacy by choosing what information to include in the dreams you post.

#### The Information We Collect

The Site allows you to create an online profile, provide content, and engage in other social networking activities.

In providing these offerings on the Site, we will ask you to create a username and password. In addition, we may collect your email address, information regarding what pages of our site you visit, your IP address, age, gender, zip code, other demographic information, and any other information you submit to us, such as by emailing us, filling out a user profile or posting information on the DBI website. We do not combine such demographic information with any personally identifiable information about you.

We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 7 or Mac OS), the domain name from which you receive Internet access, and aggregate information regarding what pages consumers access or visit.

#### Collection Of Information By Third Party Sites, Sale Partners and Sponsors

Some portions of the Site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. We encourage you to consult the privacy policies of these third party sites, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected, used, or disclosed by, these third parties.

To try to bring you advertising that is of interest to you, we may share non-personally identifiable information about you, such as demographic information, with reputable third parties that we allow to present or serve advertisements on our site. In addition, as a result of your visit to our site, such ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party ad server may collect directly from you. For more information on third party ad servers, including how you may opt out of some third party ad networks, visit [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

We sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

#### Our Use of Information Collected At Our Site and Your Choices Regarding that Use

We may use the personally information that we collect to provide you with an interactive online experience, to fulfill your requests for our services, to respond to your inquiries about our services, to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to personalize or localize your experience on our site, to allow us to make personalized recommendations of content or DBI services you may be interested in, to contact you about your account with us, or display targeted advertisements to you.

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

#### Cookies And Other Technical Information

Cookies are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data). Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser).

#### How Site Uses Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We send “cookies” to your computer primarily to enhance your online experience. For example, we may use cookies to:

  * store visitors’ preferences;
  * record session information;
  * record user-specific information, such as information on what pages users access or visit;
  * alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them;
  * record past activity at Site in order to improve our Site and services;
  * ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, if any;
  * customize Site content based on a visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

We may also use “web beacons” that monitor your use of our Site. Web beacons are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the web beacon appears, the time the page containing the web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.

#### How To Disable Cookies

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other web site. Additionally, by setting your web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, there is certain information on our site that can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content.

**BY USING THE SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND SPECIFICALLY AGREEING TO OUR USE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS AS DESCRIBED HEREIN.**

#### Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information. However, we may share your personally identifiable information and any information about the content you post to the Site, submit as part of your profile or otherwise share with us (collectively “your information”), with DBI subsidiaries and affiliates who may use the information for marketing, advertising, research and other purposes.

We may also share your information with third party service providers and contractors of DBI who perform services on our behalf. Third-party agents and contractors of DBI who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for DBI.

Notwithstanding the above, if you choose to post content on our Site (e.g., a dream), we may freely disclose to others that content and any other information you have agreed to allow us to disclose to third parties based on your account settings. You should note that if the content you post on our Site (e.g., a dream) contains names or other personally identifiable information about you or another person, that information will be disclosed to others in accordance with your account settings. For example, if you choose to share your dreams, any visitor to the Site, whether a registered user or not, will be able to view your dreams and any information it contains. You should keep this in mind when deciding what information to include in the dreams and other content you post to the Site and when setting your account settings.

We may also disclose your information in response to legal process. For example, we may disclose personally identifiable information about you in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose your information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer your information if we are acquired by or merged with another company or if our assets are acquired by another entity.

In addition, we may disclose non-personally identifying demographic information and aggregate information about Site users with third parties, including marketers and advertisers.

#### Your Ability to Access Information We Have Collected from You

Registered users of the Site may view and amend the information we maintain about them by accessing their Site profile.

We encourage you to access your customer account and profile information by signing onto our site at www.dreamscloud.com and clicking on your user profile. You may correct that information and update your interests, preferences or other portions of your user profile by entering changes in the data fields on your profile page.

#### Our Commitment To Security

We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and use the information we collect online as provided in this Privacy Policy.

Despite these precautions, however, no data security safeguards are foolproof. Identity thieves, hackers and other unauthorized individuals may find ways to obtain Personal Data. Although this is unlikely, if Company learns that any of your personally identifiable information was obtained without authorization and there is a risk of fraud or identity theft, we will notify you and take steps to mitigate any harm.

#### Notice Regarding Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes, together with a new date at the top of the Privacy Policy. If those changes are material, we will give you the chance to opt out of those changes with regard to information collected under previous versions of this privacy policy.

We encourage you to check back to this Privacy Policy periodically and review the effective date at the top of the Privacy Policy to see if the Privacy Policy has changed, so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may write us at our postal address:

Attn: Privacy Officer  
DreamsBook, Inc  
Brian K. Goodkind  
Goodkind & Florio, P.A.  
4121 La Playa Blvd.  
Coconut Grove, FL 33133 

or you may use contact us link to send us an email.
